<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>5. Creations on</title><link>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-creation/</link><description>Recent content in 5. Creations on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-creation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Developh Camp</title><link>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Developh-Camp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Developh-Camp/</guid><description>Foundations Identity &amp;amp; Practice Tatlong problema ng Pinoy creators https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dFm6EId2Tyc
Our work is undervalued All we do is make things pretty or &amp;ldquo;aesthetic&amp;rdquo; Sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to feel your Filipino-ness in your work We usually use foreign styles, elements, and languages We measure our excellence in terms of being &amp;ldquo;world class&amp;rdquo;, or the ability to gain recognition abroad What happens to our self-worth?</description></item><item><title>Dissecting Digital Design</title><link>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Dissecting-Digital-Design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Dissecting-Digital-Design/</guid><description>Notes https://space.hyperlink.academy/307974367572132425
Spaces A city is not a computer “libraries are not just places for the consumption of information and knowledge, but places for local communities to build their own collections and perform them,” Mattern tells me.</description></item><item><title>Fast Food Education</title><link>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Fast-Food-Education/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Fast-Food-Education/</guid><description>Sources [[Design Justice - Book]] [[Our Way Out - Close Collaboration Between Liberal and Vocational Education - Essay]] [[Udacitys Sebastian Thrun Godfather Of Free Online Education Changes - Essay]] [[The case study factory - Essay]] [[Resisting Distance Learning - Essay]] [[Learning to earn vs learning to learn - Essay]] [[In Online Ed Content Is No Longer King - Cohorts Are - Essay]] [[The Global Classroom - An Opportunity for Empowerment or Exploitation - Publication]] [[The Dirty Little Secrets About The Worst Coding Bootcamps Out There - Essay]] [[The McDonaldization of Education - the rise of slow - Essay]] Notes Are MOOCs, Bootcamps and Other Alternative Education Options Effective?</description></item><item><title>Level Up</title><link>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Level-Up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Level-Up/</guid><description>Sources See them all in this essay&amp;rsquo;s Are.na board
[[The Minecraft Generation - Essay]] [[Its time to build - A New Worlds Fair - Essay]] [[The Rise and Fall of Internet Art Communities - Essay]] [[On Roblox Kids Learn Its Hard to Earn Money Making Games - Essay]] [[Capitalism in virtual worlds - Essay]] [[Fortnite and Minecraft are getting kids excited about learning again - Essay]] [[Why the Metaverse Matters - Essay]] [[13 Principles of Web3 - Thread]] [[A Digtial Yggdrasil - Education as a Public Good - Proposal]] [[Content, Services, and Asset Businesses in the Metaverse - Essay]] Web3&amp;rsquo;s Educational Potential [[Deschooling Society - Book]] [[Gamification vs Pointsification - Essay]] [[Is the Metaverse Finally Emerging - Essay]] [[The Internet As Your Resume - Essay]] [[Computers and Creativity - Thesis]] [[Video Games are the Future of Education - Essay]] Ughh as much as I don&amp;rsquo;t like Meta&amp;hellip; Education in the metaverse Outlines Draft 1 How can I bring in the idea of an infinite game&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>On Digital Gardening</title><link>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/On-Digital-Gardening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/On-Digital-Gardening/</guid><description>Notes From my Are.na channels: Digital Gardens and Tools for Thought
How the Blog Broke the Web Homepages Built by hand no two were alike Dominant metaphor: table of contents &amp;gt; diary entry We all became amateur librarians Early web restrictions Online HTML knowledge Hosting account Slow shift to rapid web publishing; instead of building their own systems, users were working inside one; from manual to effortless Chronlogical Sort era/reverse chronology bias -&amp;gt; death of the old, cool, weird and hand-organized web Of Digital Streams, Campfires and Gardens How do we build and maintain our own personal information gardens?</description></item><item><title>Thesis</title><link>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Thesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.bianca.digital/5.-Creation/Thesis/</guid><description>Thesis Advisor Notes 9/12/22 Feedback Title: Currently, does not define or hint what &amp;ldquo;Collaboratively Imagining&amp;rdquo; would entail. Consider a more effective title for a future version.</description></item></channel></rss>